Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Horace Taft as dean, 1972-1975; Accession 1983-A-051
  - 1972-1973
    - Five-Year B.A. (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Forestry (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Freshman counselors, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Freshman counselors, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Future committee (Box 10, Folder 119 - 120)
    - Future committee (Box 11, Folder 121 - 122)
    - Geology and Geophysics (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - German (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Gimbel Cup (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Governance (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Grades (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Grading (Box 11, Folder 129 - 130)
    - Graduate School: tutor fees (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Graduate-Professiona1 Student Senate (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Guggenheim fellowships (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Hatch Prize (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Health Service (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Henry fellowships (Box 12, Folder 136)
    - History (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - History of Art (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - History of Science and Medicine (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - Honorary degrees (Box 12, Folder 140 - 141)
    - Honors and Special Projects (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Housing (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Human subjects (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Humanities, Council on the (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Institute for Social and Policy Studies (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Invitations (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - Job opportunities (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Joint Boards (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Joint committee B.A./M.A. (Box 13, Folder 152)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships: Natural Sciences (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships: Social Sciences (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Junior Year Abroad (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Language Committee, University (Box 13, Folder 156)
    - Law School. (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Leaves of absence (Box 13, Folder 158 - 159)
    - Leaves of absence (Box 14, Folder 160 - 161)
    - Lectors (Box 14, Folder 162)
    - Letters to answer (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Letters: general (Box 14, Folder 164 - 165)
    - Linguistics (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Literature major (Box 14, Folder 167 - 168)
    - Mathematics (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Mailing lists (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - MB and B -- Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Minority recruitment (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - Morse proposals (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - Morse Fellowships (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - Moving (Box 15, Folder 177)
    - Music at Yale (Box 15, Folder 178)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Box 15, Folder 179)
    - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 15, Folder 180)
    - New colleges (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - News Bureau releases (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) program (Box 15, Folder 183)
    - Nursing School (Box 15, Folder 184)
    - Office equipment (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - Operations, University (Box 15, Folder 186)
    - Panoramas (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - Parents -- correspondence (Box 15, Folder 188)
    - Parking (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Personnel (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Philosophy (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Philosophy and Psychology (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - Physics (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Political Science (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Pre-medical advisory (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - President's office (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - Prize Teaching Fellows (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - Programs (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - Proposals (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - Provost's office (Box 16, Folder 201)
    - Psychology (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - Publication Series, Yale College (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - Recommendations (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - Registration (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Religious Studies (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - Request for services (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - Research appointments (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - Retirements (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Romance languages (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Scholars of the House (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - Science (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Science and Engineering Association, Yale (Box 17, Folder 213)
    - Secretary's office (Box 17, Folder 214)
    - Slavic (Box 17, Folder 215)
    - Sociology (Box 17, Folder 216)
    - Southeast Asia Studies (Box 17, Folder 217)
    - Space (Box 17, Folder 218)
    - Spanish-speaking students (Box 17, Folder 219)
    - Special programs, sub-committee on (Box 17, Folder 220)
    - Special students (Box 17, Folder 221)
    - Staff (Box 17, Folder 222)
    - Statistics (Box 17, Folder 223)
    - Steering Committee (Box 17, Folder 224)
    - Students' correspondence (Box 17, Folder 225)
    - Study of the city (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Summary sheets (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - Summer programs, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 228)
    - Summer programs (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Summer programs (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - Teacher training (Box 18, Folder 231 - 232)
    - Teaching and learning (Box 18, Folder 233)
    - Teaching fellows 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - Teaching in the Residential Colleges (Box 18, Folder 235)
    - Teaching elsewhere (Box 18, Folder 236)
    - Telephones (Box 18, Folder 237)
    - Transfer students (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Treasurer's office (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Under-subscribed courses (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - U.S. Grant and Upward Bound (Box 18, Folder 241)
    - Veterans' benefits (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Visitors (Box 18, Folder 243)
    - Women at Yale (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - W.Y.B.C. radio station (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Y.C.P.S. (Box 18, Folder 247)
  - Blum Committee, 1972-1973
    - Blum (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Blum proposal (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Report draft (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Summary of Proposals (9) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Financial implications of calendar changes (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Taylor: Effect of Federal action on Graduate School (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Calendar changes and bottleneck problem (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Undergraduate residence data (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Financial gains from increased enrollment (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Proposal for an extended semester (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - The strengthened semester plan memo (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Peck letter on Management Operations (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Preliminary projection of income and expense (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Yale University 1971-1972 Budget (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Report on Computer Budget (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Committee budget (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Taft chart: Undergraduates in professional schools, 1972 June (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Notes on committee meetings (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Pierson, G.W., letter and appendix, 1972 June 9 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Erikson, Hall, Peck letter, 1972 May 5 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Committee members list, summer addresses (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Six-sixes plan (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Meyer, M., correspondence (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Oleson Report on Academic Calendars (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Fitt memo on Higher Education Bill, 1972 June 12 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Embersits: Deficit Elimination Program, 1971 November 5 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Financial memos from Graduate School (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - D. Taylor chart on early retirement (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Treasurer's reports to committee (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Student recommendations for summers (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Information requested by committee (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - 1973-1974
    - Administrative Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Data Systems (ADS), 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee on Undergraduate Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action plan, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5 - 8)
    - Affirmative Action report, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Afro-American Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Alumni, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Anthropology, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Antilles Research Program, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Applications for positions, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Appointment procedures, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Junior Appointments Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 16 - 17)
    - Senior Appointments Committee, 1973-1974
    - Senior Appointments Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Humanities, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Physical Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Social Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Biological Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 22 - 23)
    - Architecture, School of, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Art School and Art major, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Astronomy, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Auditing, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Band, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Banner Publications, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Biology, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Budgets 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 32 - 33)
    - Budget committee, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Bursar, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Campus Police, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Career Advisory Office, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Chairs, Professorial, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Chairmen, Departmental, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Chairmanships, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Chemistry, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Classics, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Co-education Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - College Council, Yale, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Combined Science Major, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Commencement, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Committees, Yale College, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Communications, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Computer Center, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Computer Science, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Computers at Yale, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Concilium, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Conferences, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Coop, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Corporation actions, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Corporation minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Council of Masters, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Course critique, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Course of study, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 61 - 64)
    - Credits, college, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Credits, course, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Culture and behavior, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Davenport College, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Dean's office staff, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Deans, College, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Deanships, College, committee, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Deans, College, applications, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Deans' conferences, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Debating, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - Development Office, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 76 - 77)
    - Dining halls, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Distributional requirements and guidelines, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Divisional major I (HAL), 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - Divisional major II, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Divisional major III, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 82)
    - Divisional major IV, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - Drama major, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 84)
    - Dramat, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Early concentration, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Early retirement, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 87)
    - East and Southeast Asian Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 89)
    - Election of students, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 90)
    - Energy, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 91)
    - Engineering and Applied Science, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 92)
    - English, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 93)
    - Enrollments, course, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 94 - 96)
    - Entertainment, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 97)
    - Examinations, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 98)
    - Executive Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 99)
    - Executive Committee (FAS), 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 100)
    - Extension school, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 101)
    - Faculty advising, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 102)
    - Faculty Club, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 103)
    - Faculty meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 104)
    - Faculty problem, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 105)
    - Fair Labor Standard Act reports, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 106)
    - Fellowships, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 107)
    - Fellowships, committee on, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 108)
    - Figure skating, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 109)
    - Film Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 110)
    - Financial aid, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 111)
    - Fire, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 112)
    - Five-year B.A., 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 113)
    - Forestry, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 114)
    - French, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 116)
    - Freshmen, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 117)
    - Freshmen counselors, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 118)
    - Freshman essay proposal, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 119)
    - Geology and Geophysics, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 120)
    - German, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 121)
    - Governance, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 123)
    - Grades, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 124)
    - Grading, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 125)
    - Graduate School -- tutor fees, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 126)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 127)
    - Grounds maintenance, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 128)
    - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 129)
    - Hatch Prize, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 130)
    - Yale Health Service, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 131)
    - History, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 132)
    - History of Art, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 133)
    - History of Science and Medicine, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 134)
    - Honorary degrees, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 135)
    - Honors and Special Projects, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 136)
    - Housing, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 137)
    - Humanities, Council of the, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 138)
    - Humanities Council, Connecticut, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 139)
    - Humanities, special courses in, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 140)
    - Humanities Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 141)
    - Information pamphlet, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 142)
    - Institute for Social and Policy Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 143)
    - Institutional Research, Office of, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 144)
    - Internship programs, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 145)
    - Introductory seminar program, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 146)
    - Invitations, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 147)
    - Islamic Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 148)
    - Italian, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 149)
    - Joint Committee on B.A./M.A., 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 150)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships, Natural Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 151)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships, Social Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 152)
    - Junior Year Abroad, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 153)
    - Labor negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 154)
    - Language Committee, University, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 155)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 156)
    - Latin-American Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 157)
    - Leaves of absence (students), 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 158)
    - Leaves of absence (faculty), 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 159)
    - Letters, general, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 160)
    - Library, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 161)
    - Linguistics, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 162)
    - Literature major, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 163)
    - Literature major, Combined, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 164)
    - Mathematics, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 165)
    - Medical School, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 166)
    - Mellon Fellows (Aspen), 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 167)
    - Military, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 168)
    - Minority recruitment, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 169)
    - Minority students, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 170)
    - Miscellaneous lists, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 171)
    - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (MB and B), 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 172)
    - Morse Cordite, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 176)
    - Morse proposals, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 177)
    - Music at Yale, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 178)
    - News Bureau releases, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 179)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 180)
    - Old Dominion (budget), 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 181)
    - University operations, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 182)
    - Orientation program, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 183)
    - Parents: correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 184)
    - Parking, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 185)
    - Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 186)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 187)
    - Philosophy, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 188)
    - Philosophy and Psychology, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 189)
    - Physics, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 190)
    - Political Science, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 191)
    - Political Union, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 192)
    - Pre-medical advisory, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 193)
    - President's office, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 194)
    - Undergraduate prizes, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 195)
    - Prize teaching, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 196 - 198)
    - Pre-orientation registration program (PROP), 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 199)
    - Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 200)
    - Provost's office, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 201)
    - Psychology, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 202)
    - Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 203)
    - Registrar's office, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 204)
    - Registration -- Registrar, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 205)
    - Religious Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 206)
    - Research appointments, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 207)
    - Resident Fellows requests, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 208 - 209)
    - Residential College personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 210)
    - Retirements, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 211)
    - St. John's College, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 212)
    - Salaries, faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 213)
    - Scholars of the House, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 214)
    - Science, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 215)
    - Secretary's office, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 216)
    - Seven Springs Farm, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 217)
    - Shockley affair, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 218 - 219)
    - Shockley affair, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 220)
    - Slavic, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 221)
    - Sociology, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 222)
    - Space, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 223)
    - Spanish, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 224)
    - Special students, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 225)
    - Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 226)
    - Steering committee, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 227)
    - Stock requests, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 228)
    - Students' letters, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 229)
    - Students, non-Yale, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 230)
    - Study of the city, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 231)
    - Summer programs, applications and budgets, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 232)
    - Summer programs 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 233)
    - Taft, Horace D., personal, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 234)
    - Tea service, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 235)
    - Teaching and Learning, committee on, report, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 236 - 237)
    - Teaching and learning, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 238 - 240)
    - Teaching elsewhere, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 241)
    - Teacher preparation, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 242)
    - Telephones, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 243)
    - TIAA - CREF, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 244)
    - Travel policy, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 245)
    - Treasurer's office, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 246)
    - Tuition postponement option, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 247)
    - Undergraduate affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 249)
    - Undergraduate regulations, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 250)
    - University Council, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 251)
    - Visitors, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 252)
    - Wilkinson, John, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 253)
    - Women at Yale, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 254)
    - Women, Liaison committee for, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 255)
    - Yale Weekly Bulletin and calendar: Memorandum from Kingman Brewster on the Yale University Affirmative Action plan; letter of transmittal, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 256)
  - 1974-1975
    - A.B. C. -- "A Better Chance", 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Acceleration, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Acceleration and credits, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Science major, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Admissions, undergraduate, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Afro-American Studies Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Alterations, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Alumni, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - American Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Anthropology, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Applications for positions, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Appointment procedures, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Appointments, junior, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Appointments Committee, Senior, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Appointments, Senior, 1974-1975
      - Biological Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Humanities, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Physical Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Social Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Architecture, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Art School and Art Major, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Associated Student Agencies, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Association of Colleges in New England, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Astronomy, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Athletics, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Audio-visual, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Aurelian Society, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Awards, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Benefits, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Biology, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - British Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Budget committee, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 32 - 34)
    - Bursar, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Calendar, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Campus Police, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Career Advisory Office, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Chairmen: departmental, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Chemistry, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Classics, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - College Counci1, Yale, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Combined Literature major, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Combined Science major, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Commencement, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Communications, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Comparative Literature, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - Computer Science, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - Concilium, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Conferences, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Coop, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - Corporation actions, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Corporation minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Council of Masters, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Course credits, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - Course of study, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 57 - 60)
    - Course of study II, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 61 - 63)